[
  {
    "id": "8925",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Built-in Algorithms Inputs",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "______ expects a single preprocessed text file with space-separated tokens. Each line in the file should contain a single sentence.",
      "answers": [
        "Blazing Text",
        "DeepAR",
        "Factorization Machines",
        "Image Classification",
        "IP Insights",
        "K-Means",
        "K-Nearest Neighbors",
        "Latent Dirichlet Allocation (LDA)",
        "Linear Learner",
        "Neural Topic Model (NTM)",
        "Object2Vec",
        "Object Detection",
        "Principal Component Analysis (PCA)",
        "Random Cut Forest (RCF)",
        "Semantic Segmentation",
        "Sequence-to-Sequence",
        "XGBoost"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Blazing Text"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "8926",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Built-in Algorithms Inputs",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "DeepAR expects training and test datasets in ______ format. Files can be in gzip or Parquet file format.",
      "answers": [
        "JSON Lines",
        "recordIO-protobuf",
        "x-recordio-protobuf",
        "application/json",
        "RecordIO (application/x-recordio)",
        "image (image/png, image/jpeg, and application/x-image)",
        "text/csv",
        "text/libsvm",
        "application/jsonlines",
        "recordIO-wrapped-protobuf",
        "application/x-recordio-protobuf",
        "application/x-image",
        "image/jpeg",
        "gzip or Parquet"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["JSON Lines"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "8927",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Built-in Algorithms Inputs",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "DeepAR expects files can be in ______ file format.",
      "answers": [
        "JSON Lines",
        "recordIO-protobuf",
        "x-recordio-protobuf",
        "application/json",
        "RecordIO (application/x-recordio)",
        "image (image/png, image/jpeg, and application/x-image)",
        "text/csv",
        "text/libsvm",
        "application/jsonlines",
        "recordIO-wrapped-protobuf",
        "application/x-recordio-protobuf",
        "application/x-image",
        "image/jpeg",
        "gzip or Parquet"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["gzip or Parquet"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "8928",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Built-in Algorithms Inputs",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "For inference, Factorization Machines support the ______ and ______ formats.",
      "answers": [
        "JSON Lines",
        "recordIO-protobuf",
        "x-recordio-protobuf",
        "application/json",
        "RecordIO (application/x-recordio)",
        "image (image/png, image/jpeg, and application/x-image)",
        "text/csv",
        "text/libsvm",
        "application/jsonlines",
        "recordIO-wrapped-protobuf",
        "application/x-recordio-protobuf",
        "application/x-image",
        "image/jpeg",
        "gzip or Parquet"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["application/json", "x-recordio-protobuf"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "8929",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Built-in Algorithms Inputs",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 3",
      "question": "The Amazon SageMaker Image Classification algorithm supports both ______ and ______ content types for training in file mode, and supports the ______ content type for training in pipe mode. ",
      "answers": [
        "JSON Lines",
        "recordIO-protobuf",
        "x-recordio-protobuf",
        "application/json",
        "RecordIO (application/x-recordio)",
        "image (image/png, image/jpeg, and application/x-image)",
        "text/csv",
        "text/libsvm",
        "application/jsonlines",
        "recordIO-wrapped-protobuf",
        "application/x-recordio-protobuf",
        "application/x-image",
        "image/jpeg",
        "gzip or Parquet"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["RecordIO (application/x-recordio)", "image (image/png, image/jpeg, and application/x-image)", "RecordIO (application/x-recordio)"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "8930",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Built-in Algorithms Inputs",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "IP Insights expects training and validation data content types need to be in ______ format. ",
      "answers": [
        "JSON Lines",
        "recordIO-protobuf",
        "x-recordio-protobuf",
        "application/json",
        "RecordIO (application/x-recordio)",
        "image (image/png, image/jpeg, and application/x-image)",
        "text/csv",
        "text/libsvm",
        "application/jsonlines",
        "recordIO-wrapped-protobuf",
        "application/x-recordio-protobuf",
        "application/x-image",
        "image/jpeg",
        "gzip or Parquet"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["text/csv"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "8931",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Built-in Algorithms Inputs",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 3",
      "question": "For inference, IP Insights supports ______, ______, and ______ data content types. ",
      "answers": [
        "JSON Lines",
        "recordIO-protobuf",
        "x-recordio-protobuf",
        "application/json",
        "RecordIO (application/x-recordio)",
        "image (image/png, image/jpeg, and application/x-image)",
        "text/csv",
        "text/libsvm",
        "application/jsonlines",
        "recordIO-wrapped-protobuf",
        "application/x-recordio-protobuf",
        "application/x-image",
        "image/jpeg",
        "gzip or Parquet"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["text/csv", "application/json", "application/jsonlines"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "8932",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Built-in Algorithms Inputs",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "K-Means supports both ______ and ______ formats for training.",
      "answers": [
        "JSON Lines",
        "recordIO-protobuf",
        "x-recordio-protobuf",
        "application/json",
        "RecordIO (application/x-recordio)",
        "image (image/png, image/jpeg, and application/x-image)",
        "text/csv",
        "text/libsvm",
        "application/jsonlines",
        "recordIO-wrapped-protobuf",
        "application/x-recordio-protobuf",
        "application/x-image",
        "image/jpeg",
        "gzip or Parquet"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["recordIO-wrapped-protobuf","text/csv"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "8933",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Built-in Algorithms Inputs",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 3",
      "question": "For inference, K-Means supports ______, ______, and ______ .",
      "answers": [
        "JSON Lines",
        "recordIO-protobuf",
        "x-recordio-protobuf",
        "application/json",
        "RecordIO (application/x-recordio)",
        "image (image/png, image/jpeg, and application/x-image)",
        "text/csv",
        "text/libsvm",
        "application/jsonlines",
        "recordIO-wrapped-protobuf",
        "application/x-recordio-protobuf",
        "application/x-image",
        "image/jpeg",
        "gzip or Parquet"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["text/csv", "application/json", "application/x-recordio-protobuf"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "8934",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Built-in Algorithms Inputs",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "For training inputs, K-Nearest Neighbors supports ______ and ______ data formats.",
      "answers": [
        "JSON Lines",
        "recordIO-protobuf",
        "x-recordio-protobuf",
        "application/json",
        "RecordIO (application/x-recordio)",
        "image (image/png, image/jpeg, and application/x-image)",
        "text/csv",
        "text/libsvm",
        "application/jsonlines",
        "recordIO-wrapped-protobuf",
        "application/x-recordio-protobuf",
        "application/x-image",
        "image/jpeg",
        "gzip or Parquet"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["text/csv", "application/x-recordio-protobuf"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "8935",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Built-in Algorithms Inputs",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 3",
      "question": "For inference inputs, K-Nearest Neighbors supports the ______, ______, and ______ data formats. ",
      "answers": [
        "JSON Lines",
        "recordIO-protobuf",
        "x-recordio-protobuf",
        "application/json",
        "RecordIO (application/x-recordio)",
        "image (image/png, image/jpeg, and application/x-image)",
        "text/csv",
        "text/libsvm",
        "application/jsonlines",
        "recordIO-wrapped-protobuf",
        "application/x-recordio-protobuf",
        "application/x-image",
        "image/jpeg",
        "gzip or Parquet"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["application/json", "application/x-recordio-protobuf", "text/csv"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "8936",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Built-in Algorithms Inputs",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "Latent Dirichlet Allocation (LDA) supports both ______ (dense and sparse) and ______ file formats.",
      "answers": [
        "JSON Lines",
        "recordIO-protobuf",
        "x-recordio-protobuf",
        "application/json",
        "RecordIO (application/x-recordio)",
        "image (image/png, image/jpeg, and application/x-image)",
        "text/csv",
        "text/libsvm",
        "application/jsonlines",
        "recordIO-wrapped-protobuf",
        "application/x-recordio-protobuf",
        "application/x-image",
        "image/jpeg",
        "gzip or Parquet"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["recordIO-wrapped-protobuf", "text/csv"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "8937",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Built-in Algorithms Inputs",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 3",
      "question": "For inference, Latent Dirichlet Allocation (LDA) supports ______, ______, and ______ content types. ",
      "answers": [
        "JSON Lines",
        "recordIO-protobuf",
        "x-recordio-protobuf",
        "application/json",
        "RecordIO (application/x-recordio)",
        "image (image/png, image/jpeg, and application/x-image)",
        "text/csv",
        "text/libsvm",
        "application/jsonlines",
        "recordIO-wrapped-protobuf",
        "application/x-recordio-protobuf",
        "application/x-image",
        "image/jpeg",
        "gzip or Parquet"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["text/csv", "application/json", "application/x-recordio-protobuf"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "8938",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Built-in Algorithms Inputs",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "For training, the Linear Learner algorithm supports both ______ and ______ formats. ",
      "answers": [
        "JSON Lines",
        "recordIO-protobuf",
        "x-recordio-protobuf",
        "application/json",
        "RecordIO (application/x-recordio)",
        "image (image/png, image/jpeg, and application/x-image)",
        "text/csv",
        "text/libsvm",
        "application/jsonlines",
        "recordIO-wrapped-protobuf",
        "application/x-recordio-protobuf",
        "application/x-image",
        "image/jpeg",
        "gzip or Parquet"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["recordIO-wrapped-protobuf", "text/csv"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "8939",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Built-in Algorithms Inputs",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 3",
      "question": "For inference, the Linear Learner algorithm supports the ______, ______, and ______ formats. ",
      "answers": [
        "JSON Lines",
        "recordIO-protobuf",
        "x-recordio-protobuf",
        "application/json",
        "RecordIO (application/x-recordio)",
        "image (image/png, image/jpeg, and application/x-image)",
        "text/csv",
        "text/libsvm",
        "application/jsonlines",
        "recordIO-wrapped-protobuf",
        "application/x-recordio-protobuf",
        "application/x-image",
        "image/jpeg",
        "gzip or Parquet"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["application/json", "application/x-recordio-protobuf", "text/csv"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "8940",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Built-in Algorithms Inputs",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "The train, validation, and test data channels for Neural Topic Model (NTM) support both ______ (dense and sparse) and ______ file formats. ",
      "answers": [
        "JSON Lines",
        "recordIO-protobuf",
        "x-recordio-protobuf",
        "application/json",
        "RecordIO (application/x-recordio)",
        "image (image/png, image/jpeg, and application/x-image)",
        "text/csv",
        "text/libsvm",
        "application/jsonlines",
        "recordIO-wrapped-protobuf",
        "application/x-recordio-protobuf",
        "application/x-image",
        "image/jpeg",
        "gzip or Parquet"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["recordIO-wrapped-protobuf", "text/csv"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "8941",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Built-in Algorithms Inputs",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 4",
      "question": "For inference, Neural Topic Model (NTM) supports ______, ______, ______, and ______ content types.",
      "answers": [
        "JSON Lines",
        "recordIO-protobuf",
        "x-recordio-protobuf",
        "application/json",
        "RecordIO (application/x-recordio)",
        "image (image/png, image/jpeg, and application/x-image)",
        "text/csv",
        "text/libsvm",
        "application/jsonlines",
        "recordIO-wrapped-protobuf",
        "application/x-recordio-protobuf",
        "application/x-image",
        "image/jpeg",
        "gzip or Parquet"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["text/csv", "application/json", "application/jsonlines", "application/x-recordio-protobuf"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "8943",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Built-in Algorithms Inputs",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "The Amazon SageMaker Object Detection algorithm supports both ______ and ______ content types.",
      "answers": [
        "JSON Lines",
        "recordIO-protobuf",
        "x-recordio-protobuf",
        "application/json",
        "RecordIO (application/x-recordio)",
        "image (image/png, image/jpeg, and application/x-image)",
        "text/csv",
        "text/libsvm",
        "application/jsonlines",
        "recordIO-wrapped-protobuf",
        "application/x-recordio-protobuf",
        "application/x-image",
        "image/jpeg",
        "gzip or Parquet"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["RecordIO (application/x-recordio)", "image (image/png, image/jpeg, and application/x-image)"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "8944",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Built-in Algorithms Inputs",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "Principal Component Analysis (PCA) supports both ______ and ______ formats are supported.",
      "answers": [
        "JSON Lines",
        "recordIO-protobuf",
        "x-recordio-protobuf",
        "application/json",
        "RecordIO (application/x-recordio)",
        "image (image/png, image/jpeg, and application/x-image)",
        "text/csv",
        "text/libsvm",
        "application/jsonlines",
        "recordIO-wrapped-protobuf",
        "application/x-recordio-protobuf",
        "application/x-image",
        "image/jpeg",
        "gzip or Parquet"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["recordIO-wrapped-protobuf", "text/csv"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "8945",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Built-in Algorithms Inputs",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 3",
      "question": "For inference, Principal Component Analysis (PCA) supports ______, ______, and ______. ",
      "answers": [
        "JSON Lines",
        "recordIO-protobuf",
        "x-recordio-protobuf",
        "application/json",
        "RecordIO (application/x-recordio)",
        "image (image/png, image/jpeg, and application/x-image)",
        "text/csv",
        "text/libsvm",
        "application/jsonlines",
        "recordIO-wrapped-protobuf",
        "application/x-recordio-protobuf",
        "application/x-image",
        "image/jpeg",
        "gzip or Parquet"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["text/csv", "application/json", "application/x-recordio-protobuf"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "8946",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Built-in Algorithms Inputs",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "For Random Cut Forest (RCF), train and test data content types can be either ______ or ______ formats. ",
      "answers": [
        "JSON Lines",
        "recordIO-protobuf",
        "x-recordio-protobuf",
        "application/json",
        "RecordIO (application/x-recordio)",
        "image (image/png, image/jpeg, and application/x-image)",
        "text/csv",
        "text/libsvm",
        "application/jsonlines",
        "recordIO-wrapped-protobuf",
        "application/x-recordio-protobuf",
        "application/x-image",
        "image/jpeg",
        "gzip or Parquet"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["application/x-recordio-protobuf", "text/csv"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "8947",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Built-in Algorithms Inputs",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "Semantic Segmentation supports the augmented manifest image format ______ for training in Pipe input mode straight from Amazon S3. For inference, an endpoint accepts images with an ______ content type.",
      "answers": [
        "JSON Lines",
        "recordIO-protobuf",
        "x-recordio-protobuf",
        "application/json",
        "RecordIO (application/x-recordio)",
        "image (image/png, image/jpeg, and application/x-image)",
        "text/csv",
        "text/libsvm",
        "application/jsonlines",
        "recordIO-wrapped-protobuf",
        "application/x-recordio-protobuf",
        "application/x-image",
        "image/jpeg",
        "gzip or Parquet"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["application/x-image", "image/jpeg"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "8948",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Built-in Algorithms Inputs",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Amazon SageMaker Sequence-to-Sequence expects data in ______ format. However, the tokens are expected as integers, not as floating points, as is usually the case.",
      "answers": [
        "JSON Lines",
        "recordIO-protobuf",
        "x-recordio-protobuf",
        "application/json",
        "RecordIO (application/x-recordio)",
        "image (image/png, image/jpeg, and application/x-image)",
        "text/csv",
        "text/libsvm",
        "application/jsonlines",
        "recordIO-wrapped-protobuf",
        "application/x-recordio-protobuf",
        "application/x-image",
        "image/jpeg",
        "gzip or Parquet"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["x-recordio-protobuf"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "8949",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Built-in Algorithms Inputs",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "With Sequence-to-Sequence, for hosted endpoints, inference supports two data formats. To perform inference using space separated text tokens, use the ______ format. Otherwise, use the ______ format to work with the integer encoded data.",
      "answers": [
        "JSON Lines",
        "recordIO-protobuf",
        "x-recordio-protobuf",
        "application/json",
        "RecordIO (application/x-recordio)",
        "image (image/png, image/jpeg, and application/x-image)",
        "text/csv",
        "text/libsvm",
        "application/jsonlines",
        "recordIO-wrapped-protobuf",
        "application/x-recordio-protobuf",
        "application/x-image",
        "image/jpeg",
        "gzip or Parquet"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["application/json", "x-recordio-protobuf"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "8950",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Built-in Algorithms Inputs",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "With XGBoost, for Training ContentType, valid inputs are ______ (default) or ______.",
      "answers": [
        "JSON Lines",
        "recordIO-protobuf",
        "x-recordio-protobuf",
        "application/json",
        "RecordIO (application/x-recordio)",
        "image (image/png, image/jpeg, and application/x-image)",
        "text/csv",
        "text/libsvm",
        "application/jsonlines",
        "recordIO-wrapped-protobuf",
        "application/x-recordio-protobuf",
        "application/x-image",
        "image/jpeg",
        "gzip or Parquet"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["text/libsvm", "text/csv"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "8951",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Built-in Algorithms Inputs",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "With XGBoost, for Inference ContentType, valid inputs are text/libsvm (default) or text/csv.",
      "answers": [
        "JSON Lines",
        "recordIO-protobuf",
        "x-recordio-protobuf",
        "application/json",
        "RecordIO (application/x-recordio)",
        "image (image/png, image/jpeg, and application/x-image)",
        "text/csv",
        "text/libsvm",
        "application/jsonlines",
        "recordIO-wrapped-protobuf",
        "application/x-recordio-protobuf",
        "application/x-image",
        "image/jpeg",
        "gzip or Parquet"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["text/libsvm", "text/csv"]
    }
  }
]